Kanika Lakhanpal

Digital Content Writer

I am a digital content writer who believes in the power and magic of words. Since childhood, I have found myself deeply interested in the art of writing. Writing is a powerful tool. With great imagination in mind, you can almost bring life to words and help greatly or content writing. As a journalism and English honors student, I hope to provide my best foot forward in creating better stories and content and would love to gain and experience a new world..



kanika23.lakhanpal@gmail.com

7987627262

262

Mumbai, India

•

linkedin.com/in/kanika-lakhanpal-692200145

692200145

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Content Writer Hindustan Times Media Limited

05/2022 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Content Writer for the B2B organization
- Perform email marketing as well as curate content for LinkedIn inmails
- Handle and manage excel Database of clients
- Populate list of Clients from tools such as Lusha & Fundoo

Associate Content WriterJet Set Career

03/2022 - 05/2022

Remote

Remote

Achievements/Tasks

- Curated technical Content for the organization.
- Curated projects on topics such as LinkedIn Lead Generation.
- Created content for tutoring and teaching.

Content Editor

Men's World Magazine

04/2022 - 05/2022

Remote

Achievements/Tasks

- Structured print content into digital Content.
- Designed numerous digital marketing campaigns.
- Took part in company's rebranding.

Social Media Intern (Content Writing)Redwood Algorithms

04/2021 - 08/2021

Remote

Achievements/Tasks

- Designed numerous marketing campaigns for the organization.
- Curated content for various clients with in the company.
- Managed three social media accounts (client) at once.
- Prepared technical articles as well as creative articles for the company.
- Especially handled all the marketing functioning of Kaizen South Asia.
- Written many captions as well as image content for social media presence.

SKILLS

Content Writing			
Creative writing			
Storyboarding			
Blogging			0
SEO			0
Social Media Marketing			0
Email Marketing			0
Database management			0
Canva			0
Public Speaking			
Excellent Communication			
Team Management			

ACHIEVEMENTS

RJ HUNT Rank-2

Inter State debate competetion-1st Rank

A+ Certificate NCC

Certificate of excellence in Co-curricular area

1st Rank in Sangeet Aayojan Pratiyogita

1 st Rank in Rose Society Event

1st Rank in Inter college Debate

Kanika Lakhanpal

Digital Content Writer



kanika23.lakhanpal@gmail.com

7987627262

Mumbai, India

linkedin.com/in/kanika-lakhanpal-692200145

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Writer Scicomm India

05/2022 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Subject Matter Expert for many clients.
- Built more than 20 guizzes for graduates and postgraduates in a month.
- Built research-based content worth 45000 words for each topic.

Content Writer Intern

The Research Pedia

04/2021 - 05/2021

Achievements/Tasks

- Built highly researched most-sought articles.
- Curated more than 25000 words in a month.
- Written more than 35 statistical-based articles in a month.

EDUCATION BA (ENGLISH MAJOR) IGNOU

01/2018 - 06/2021

Courses

Minored with Psychology

Cultivated 7.25 CGPA

BJMC

Amity University

08/2017 - 08/2021

Courses

- Wrote dissertation on relations between media and its voting population.
- Event Management Team.
- Cultivated 8.25 Cgpa.

Maharishi Dayanand Public School

04/2016 - 04/2015

7.25 CGPA

10th

DAV Centenary Public School

Courses

9.0 CGPA

EXPOSURE

Volunteered for Jaipur Literature Festival 2018 and worked as a special Assistant to late CM Sheila Dixit, along with Sharmila Tagore, Soha Ali Khan, Anurag Kashyap, and more.

Volunteered for "Tik-Tok For good" as a content writer.

KEY SKILLS

I am a quick learner with strong memory and quick wit. I am adaptive and keen on flexibility. I believe myself to be a good communicator with quality management skills. I have an optimistic approach to life.

LANGUAGES

English Hindi

INTERESTS

